http://www.hrc.com/privacy-and-security-policy.cfm

Loading...
OUR POLICY IS VERY SIMPLE
We never rent, trade or sell your personal information to anyone. Period.
PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED ONLINE
We do not monitor or collect information about our visitors. The statistics we gather to understand our website usages are not associated with your personal information.
If you sign up for our newsletters, webinars, etc, we ask for information about you to best serve you. For example, we will use this information to reply to your requests, process enrollments, inform you about our services, etc. When you enroll in one of our courses or make a purchase, you will be asked to supply your billing information.OUR COMMITMENT TO ONLINE SECURITYHRC has policies and procedures in place to safeguard the security and integrity of the information you submit. All HRC consultants, support staff and subcontractors with access to personal information agree to adhere to our policy.Please note that this policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, which is beyond our control, nor does it apply to the practices of companies HRC does not own or control, or to individuals HRC does not employ or manage. You can be assured that we only use payment services that are known to keep your information secure and safe by utilizing the highest level of encryption and anti-fraud technology available.If you have any questions about our Privacy and Security Policy, contact us.
PROVEN, PRAGMATIC
Contact us to learn more about how we can help you
Contact HRC® Today
©2020 HRC® Consulting Services. All Rights Reserved.
Web by Snazzo
Admin Login
Privacy Policy •
Copyright & Disclaimer
